estatik.net 2016-04-18

# Privacy Policy - Estatik

This privacy policy describes how Estatik collects and uses privacy information from Estatik customers and website visitors.

**What information we collect**

In order to provide You services and products, Estatik may collect the following information:

_Personal information_ collected by Estatik team:

  * Name and contact information (address, email)
  * Your feedbacks and reviews of our product/services
  * Website URLs our product is installed and used
  * Your website access data where our product is installed and used

Estatik website visitors are not obliged to provide us with any kind of information. Estatik customers can provide us with information they decide to give us.

_Non-personal_ information collected by computer:

  * Cookies – small pieces of information sent from [www.estatik.net](https://estatik.net/) and stored in Your browser while You are browsing our website. Cookies help Estatik identify You as an individual. Mostly browsers automatically allow to accept cookies but You can change Your browser settings and reject [www.estatik.net](https://estatik.net/) cookies.

**What we do with information**

In general we need this information for improving our products and services, namely:

  * Learn about most needed and urgent features/products/services You would like to use on [www.estatik.net](https://estatik.net/)
  * Provide You support service, fix any bugs/issues
  * Offer You new products/services as well as notify about sales, best deals, etc.

Estatik customer can always decide whether he wants to receive our marketing emails or not, and use Unsubscribe button to reject Estatik newsletters.

**How we protect information**

All information gathered from Estatik customers is stricktly confidential. We do not distribute, sell, share Your personal information with third parties without Your permission.

Estatik applies all standard measures to protect the information You give us, namely: data encryption, password protected access to Users’ personal information, encrypted transfer of sensitive data submitted by the User through order forms, login forms etc.

#### Links to other websites

Estatik website can contain links to other websites which are not within our control. These websites contain their Privacy policies and You should check it before providing your personal information on these websites. Estatik is not reponsible for information You leave on 3d party websites.

Estatik reserves the right to change Privacy Policy at any time without prior notifications.
